Finding Aid for the Motion Picture Advertising Ephemera PASC.0160
UCLA Library Special Collections
- LEGEND OF THE LONE RANGER, THE,., 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Press book encased in card board old west style saddle bag.
- LEPER,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  Fold out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary in English, French, and German, and director's filmography.
- LIBERATION,., no date (Box 3, Folder 46)
  3 programmes: part3-The Direction of the Main Attack, part4-Battle for Berlin, part5-The Last Assault. Each includes pictures of scenes, and story summary in Russian, English, French, Spanish.
- LIGHT THAT FAILED, THE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 35)
  Fold-out programme. Includes text about players and text "Vital Statistics."
- LITTLE MISS MARKER,., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- LIVELONG WEEK, THE,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Fold out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary in English, German, French, and filmography of director.
- LOGAN'S RUN,., no date (Box 16, Folder 6)
- LONG DAY'S JOURNEY INTO NIGHT,., no date (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Souvenir book. Includes information about players and creators.
- LORD JIM,., no date (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes and text- the production, the story, and information about the players and author.
- LUCKY LADY,., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- LUST FOR LIFE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 33)
  Fold-out programme/invitation to premiere.
- MACARTHUR,., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Fold-out programme. Includes dates of key events in MacArthur's life and pictures of scenes.
- MADAME BOVARY THAT'S ME,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- MADAME CURIE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Fold-out programme. Includes text "Facts about the motion picture".
- MAGIC CHRISTIAN, THE,., no date (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes and story synopsis in English, French, and Spanish.
- MAN IN THE WILDERNESS, THE,., no date (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Fold-out ad with leather one-tooth necklace attached.
- MAN OF MARBLE,., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  Fold-out programme. Includes story summary in English, French and German, pictures from scenes, and director's filmography.
- MAN WHO WOULD BE KING, THE,., no date (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Fold-out programme. Includes information about Kipling and his writing of the story.
- MAROONED,., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes, credits, story synopsis, and information on creative talent.
- MASTER GUNFIGHTER, THE,., no date (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Souvenir program uniquely shaped. Includes credits, cast and information about production, cast and story.
- MATHILDA'S BIRTHDAY,., no date (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes and story summary in English, French, German, and Russian.
- MAYERLING,., no date (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Souvenir program. Fragile-oversize bound program that includes picture of lead characters and text in French.
- MAZEPA,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes, and story summary in English, French, and German.
- MERMAIDS,., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Ad gimmick- "Mrs. Flax's Fun Fingerfoods." "Recipes from Mrs. Flax's most creative concoctions."
- METAMORPHOSES,., no date (Box 1, Folder 49)
  Fold-out programme. Opens into a poster.
- METEOR,., no date (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary and production information.
- METRO-GOLDWYN-MAYER,., no date (Box 12, Folder 2)
  "Facts about M-G-M" up to 1953.
- METRO-GOLDWYN-MAYER,., 1946 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Production Facts. Booklet includes story synopsis and player information about 27 films.
- METRO-GOLDWYN-MAYER,., no date (Box 12, Folder 2)
  "The Year of the Lion '58 '59." Preview of productions. Booklet of miniature sample posters.
- METRO-GOLDWYN-MAYER,., no date (Box 12, Folder 3)
  "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayers presents 61/62." Preview of productions 1961-62. Booklet of miniature sample posters.
- METRO-GOLDWYN-MAYER,., no date (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Preview of productions 1960-61. Booklet of miniature sample posters.
- METRO-GOLDWYN-MAYER,., no date (Box 12, Folder 3)
  "This is the year of the Lion 1965.1966." Preview of productions.
- METRO-GOLDWYN-MAYER,., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  MGM/UA Academy screening schedules.
- METRO-GOLDWYN-MAYER,., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Fold-out preview of productions. 4 pictures of sample size posters.
- MIDSUMMERS NIGHT'S DREAM, A,., 1935 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Souvenir programme. 2 items in elaborate binding. Torn and damaged but readable. Includes pictures of players.
- MIDWAY,., no date (Box 1, Folder 47)
- MILLERS CROSSING,., 1990 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  Souvenir programme. Primarily pictorial. Pictures include captions with information about main characters and players.
- MILLIONAIRE, THE,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures from scenes, director's filmography, and story summary in English, French, and German.
- MOLLY MAGUIRES, THE,., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Souvenir book. "An attempt to recapture.the filming of The Molly Maguires." Includes green tinted pictures at different stages of production.
- MOMENT BY MOMENT,., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- MONSIGNOR,., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- MONSTER CALENDAR, THE,., 1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Calendar compiled & written by Richard Meyers, illustrated by Craig W. Rogers, cover design by Liz Shaw. Information and illustrations specific to Monster films.
- MORE AMERICAN GRAFFITI,., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Fold out programme.
- MOUNTAINS OF THE MOON,., no date (Box 9, Folder 1)
- MOVIE MOVIE,., no date (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Special press kit. Includes credits and career information on creative talent. 3 separate items- 2 poster size inserts w/captioned pictures of scenes from film. Info on M. Starger and T. Van Devere.
- MOVING VIOLATIONS,., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Ad gimmick- "Drivers Handbook."
- MUTINY ON THE BOUNTY,., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Hard cover souvenir book. Includes photos of scenes, story synopsis, and information about production and creative talents.
- MY FAIR LADY,., no date (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Hard cover souvenir book. Includes color and b/w photos of scenes, credits, and information about production and creative talents.
- MY WAR-MY LOVE,., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Fold out-programme. Includes pictures of scenes and story summary in English, German, and French.
- NAME OF THE ROSE, THE,., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Elaborate fold-out counter display.
- NAPOLEON (1927),., no date (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Dec. 26, 1981-Jan. 3,1982. Souvenir programme. Includes pictures of scenes, story synopsis, and production information
- NATURAL, THE,., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Pictorial souvenir fold-out programme.
- NEW YORK, NEW YORK,., no date (Box 1, Folder 50)
- NICHOLAS AND ALEXANDRA,., no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Souvenir book. Includes photos from scenes and information about the story and players.
- NIGHTS AND DAYS,., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  Fold-out programme. Includes commentary by director and director's filmography.
- NINE TO FIVE,., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  1981 calendar.
- NINETEEN HUNDRED FORTY ONE (1941),., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NINETY NINE (99) AND 44/100% DEAD,., no date (Box 3, Folder 10)
  One page screening programme. Includes miscellaneous information about cast, producer, and director.
- NO PEACE ANYMORE,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Fold-out programme. 2 items- Insert with screen credits and story summary. Programme includes pictures from scenes, story summary in English, French and German, and director's filmography.
- NON MATRIMONIAL STORY DULSCY,., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- NUDE BOMB, THE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 50)
- OGRE D'ATHENES, L'O,., no date (Box 2, Folder 49)
  Fold-out programme. Includes text in French. English synopsis back page.
- OLIVER,., no date (Box 3, Folder 52)
  Souvenir packet of 8 placards. Pictures of scenes.
- OLIVER,., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Souvenir book. Includes photos of scenes, and text- the story, the making of the film, the source.
- OMAR MUKHTAR LION OF THE DESERT,., no date (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Fold-out programme. Advertising supplement to Variety. Includes pictures of scenes and story summary. Folds out into a poster.
- OMEN, THE,., no date (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Pictorial souvenir program. B/W pictures.
- ON THE BEACH,., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- ONION FIELD, THE,., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Fold-out programme. Brief synopsis of story, production team, cast and staff.
- OTHER SIDE OF MIDNIGHT, THE,., no date (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Pictorial souvenir programme. Pictures and captions represent story summary.
- OTHER SIDE OF THE MOUNTAIN PART 2, THE,., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  One page programme. Includes illustration of main 2 characters.
- OUR HITLER A FILM FROM GERMANY,., no date (Box 15, Folder 29)
  Souvenir programme. Includes synopsis about each of the four parts of the film.
- PAINT YOUR WAGON,., no date (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Souvenir book. Includes b/w and color pictures of scenes, and information about production and creative talents.
- PARAMOUNT,., no date (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Academy screenings for selected branches.
- PARAMOUNT,., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Academy screening announcements for selected branches.
- PARAMOUNT,., 1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  3 items- Screening for selected branches of the Academy. 2 booklets include sample posters. Fold-out calendar.
- PARENTHOOD,., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- PASSIION,., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Fold-out programme. Brief summary of story in English, French and German. Includes filmography of director.
- PEGGY SUE GOT MARRIED,., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Pictorial souvenir book. Water damaged.
- PERSONNEL,., no date (Box 2, Folder 20)
- PHANTOM OF THE PARADISE,., no date (Box 14, Folder 4)
  7 items. 1 mask, 2 menus, 1 table tent, 1 bumper sticker, press book, and flyer.
- PIANO, THE,., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Souvenir fold-out programme.
- PLACES IN THE HEART,., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- PRISONER OF ZENDA, THE,., no date (Box 3, Folder 26)
  One page programme. Includes illustration.
- PRIVATE LIVES OF ELIZABETH AND ESSEX, THE,., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Souvenir material. 24 unbound cards in hard cover folder. Text and b/w photos discussing production, ie- costumes, set, photography.
- PUBLIC EYE, THE,., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- QUO VADIS,., no date (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary, and production information.
- RAGGEDY ANN & ANDY A MUSICAL ADVENTURE,., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  One page programme. Includes illustration of characters.
- RECOLLECTIONS,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Fold-out programme. Includes b/w pictures of scenes, commentary from director in English, German, and French, and director's filmography.
- RED AND WHITE,., no date (Box 1, Folder 41)
  Fold-out programme. Includes story summary in English, French, and German and pictures from scenes.
- REMEMBER YOUR NAME,., no date (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes and synopsis in English, French, and Spanish.
- REPUBLIC PICTURE,., no date (Box 12, Folder 6)
  A division of Republic Industries. Preview of productions. Pictorial.
- RIGHT STUFF, THE,., no date (Box 7, Folder 13)
  2 items- fold out programme and pictorial souvenir book.
- RKO,., no date (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Souvenir program. RKO Studio Club First Annual Grand Ball at the Shrine Auditorium, November 7, 1935.
- RKO,., 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Invitation to A 128-Film Retrospective, 1928-1958. - LA County Museum of Art, July 8 - October 1, 1977.
- RKO,., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  RKO Studio Club- Season's Greetings. RKO-Radio Pictures Studio Club News.
- RKO,., 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  A 128-Film Retrospective, 1928-1958. Los Angeles County Museum of Art July 8 - October 1, 1977. Souvenir program.
- ROB ROY,., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- ROBE, THE,., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes and story summary. Other text includes Cinema Scope, Why I Wrote the Robe, Behind the scenes with people.
- ROBIN AND MARIAN,., no date (Box 15, Folder 8)
- ROCKY II,., no date (Box 2, Folder 63)
  Pictorial program.
- ROMEO AND JULIET,., no date (Box 5, Folder 18)
  (Souvenir book.) Directed by Renato Castellani. Includes text- a synopsis, the making of. Information about the players and director.
- ROOM WITH A SEA VIEW, A,., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- ROOM WITH A VIEW, A,., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  1987 calendar designed by Ross Culbert Holland & Lavery, Inc. specific to A Room With A View.
- RYAN'S DAUGHTER,., no date (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Stand-up counter display.
- SAME TIME NEXT YEAR,., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  One page programme. Includes pictures of lead characters.
- SAVE THE CITY,., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- SCAR, THE,., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- SCHINDLER'S LIST,., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Pictorial souvenir book. B/W photos.
- SCHINDLER'S LIST,., 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Promotional fold-out for video release.
- SEARCH FOR PARADISE,., no date (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Souvenir book. Includes location information.
- SHADOW LINE, THE,., no date (Box 2, Folder 26)
- SHARKY'S MACHINE,., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- SHERLOCK HOLMES CALENDAR,., no date (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Calendar compiled by Sean Wright, cover design by Robin Netzer. Illustrations and information specific to Sherlock Holmes.
- SIGN OF THE CROSS, THE,., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Souvenir book by Paramount Publix Corporation.
- SIMON,., no date (Box 3, Folder 30)
- SKY, THE,., 1962 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  2 fold-out ads Russian and English. Separate assorted brief critic comments, a publicity synopsis, and a letter from Amos Vogel to Vassillia Drakakis.
- SLAP SHOT,., no date (Box 1, Folder 27)
- SLIPPER AND THE ROSE, THE: THE STORY OF CINDERELLA,., no date (Box 1, Folder 28)
- SO FAR-SO FEAR,., no date (Box 1, Folder 39)
  Fold-out programme. Text in English and French. Includes pictures from scenes, story summary and commentary by director.
- SO FINE,., no date (Box 2, Folder 51)
  One page programme. Includes characiture illustration of Ryan O'Neal.
- SOLOMON AND SHEBA,., no date (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures from scenes and text- the production, super technirama-70, the story, and the people.
- SOUND OF MUSIC, THE,., 1965 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Souvenir book. Includes color photos of scenes, story synopsis, credits, and information on creative talents.
- SPARTACUS,., no date (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Hard cover souvenir book. Includes production information, captioned color photos of scenes, credits, and fold out illustrations of main characters.
- SPIRAL,., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  2 items- Fold-out programme- pictures of scenes, story summary in English, French, and German, and director's filmography. Pamphlet- French text.
- STAR,., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Souvenir book. Includes annotated photos of scenes, commentary about production, and information about players and creators.
- STAR IS BORN, A,., 1954 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Souvenir programme to 1983 select engagement. Ticket stub from performance at the Samuel Goldwyn Theatre in LA.
- STAR TREK,., no date (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Star Trek space ship U.S.S. Enterprise blue prints put out by Balentine Books.
- STAR WARS,., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes and brief description of characters.
- STORY OF SIN,., no date (Box 1, Folder 45)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes and story summary in Russian, English, and French.
- STROMBOLI,., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- SUITE FOR A WOOD INSTRUMENT,., no date (Box 2, Folder 19)
- SUPER-IMPOSITION,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Fold-out programme. Includes pictures of scenes, summary of story in English, French, and German, and director's filmography.
- SWASHBUCKLER,., no date (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Fold-out programme. Includes collage of pictures from scenes.
- TAMING OF THE SHREW, THE,., no date (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Souvenir book. Majority of programme is pictorial. Includes text about players and creators.
- TAP,., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  Fold-out programme. Includes small pictures of scenes, story summary, and miscellaneous information about actors.
- TARZAN FINDS A SON,., no date (Box 3, Folder 32)
  Fold-out programme. Includes text "Jungle Jottings."
- TEN COMMANDMENTS, THE,., no date (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Souvenir book. Includes color illustrations of scenes and main characters, brief information on main characters and creative talents, and story synopsis.
- THERE'S A GIRL IN MY SOUP,., no date (Box 1, Folder 2)
- THEY CAME TO CORDURA,., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  4 items: a review found in the Hollywood Reporter, 3 pictures: Gary Cooper, Richard Conte, Dick York, Van Heflin.
- TIME BANDITS,., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Fold-out programme. Brief summary of story, cast, and creator.
- TOMMY,., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- TOPAZ,., no date (Box 2, Folder 46)
  Fold-out programme in the shape of Hitchcock profile. Includes text "production notes."
- TRADER HORN,., 1931 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Souvenir programme from Graumans Chinese Theatre.
- TRIBUTE TO DAVID L. WOLPER; A,., no date (Box 3, Folder 47)
  One page programme. The Gallery of Modern Art, including the Huntington Hartford Collection presents A Tribute To David L. Wolper. Dates and times of screenings.
- TWENTIETH CENTURY FOX,., 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  Preview of productions for 1977. Booklet of sample posters.
- TWENTIETH CENTURY FOX,., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  "It's Gonna Be A Hot Summer." Advertising supplement to Variety. Preview of productions. Booklet of sample posters.
- TWENTIETH CENTURY FOX,., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  Academy membership screening schedule. Miniature samples of posters.
- TWENTIETH CENTURY FOX,., no date (Box 12, Folder 13)
  "A Legacy for Tomorrow." Brochure reflects future projects.
- TYCOON, THE,., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  One page programme. Includes illustrated pictures from scenes.
- UNITED ARTISTS,., no date (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Preview of releases.
- UNITED ARTISTS,., 1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Preview of releases. Includes b/w photos and brief annotations.
- UNITED ARTISTS,., 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Advertising supplement to Variety, December 22,1976. United Artists 25. Preview of productions.
- UNIVERSAL,., no date (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Production Report. First half of '42-'43 releases. Mini illustration of lot and what is happening.
- UNIVERSAL,., 1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  "On The Way to You From Universal. Preview of productions. Oversized booklet includes samples of posters.
- UNIVERSAL,., no date (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Studio screening calendar for Academy members in selected branches.
- UNIVERSAL,., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Universal Pictures for 1982. Advertising supplement to Variety. Oversize booklet includes samples of posters.
- UNIVERSAL,., no date (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Dino De Laurentiis Corp acquisition of motion picture rights for Conan novels in association with Universal. Includes a picture featuring 24 Conan book covers.
- VIA MAX,., no date (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Pictorial souvenir book. Last page text in Spanish and German.
- VIRGINIA CITY,., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Souvenir fold-out programme of guests aboard Warner Brother's "Virginia City Premiere Special, Southern Pacific Lines."
- VITAPHONE,., 1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  The Institute of the Musical, Inc. presents The 50th Anniversary of Vitaphone 1926-1976.
- WALK IN THE CLOUDS, A,., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Fold-out programme provides cast and credit information.
- WALT DISNEY PRODUCTIONS,., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  Walt Disney Productions presents its feature film releases for 1982.Oversize booklet of sample posters.
- WAR OF THE ROSES, THE,., 1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Unique press kit in the form of a photo album. Fourteen b/w 8x10 stills located in the motion picture stills collection.
- WARNER BROTHERS,., no date (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Preview of productions. Oversize booklet of samples of posters.
- WARNER BROTHERS,., no date (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Souvenir programme- National Film Theatre presents Tribute to the Warner Brothers.
- WARNER BROTHERS,., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Souvenir programme. Warner Brothers Studios-Celebration of Tradition June 2, 1990
- WATERSHIP DOWN,., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Fold-out programme. 2 inserts= yellow insert- pictures of characters/abridged rabbit dictionary & a letter from Lynda Cardoso, Films Inc. Programme has credits and text "production notes".
- WESTSIDE STORY,., no date (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Souvenir book. Includes color and b/w photos of scenes, credits, production information, story synopsis, and information about creative talent.
- WILD GEESE, THE,., no date (Box 6, Folder 10)
  2 items- souvenir book and fold-out programme. Souvenir book includes photos of scenes, and information about characters and creators.
- WILLOW,., 1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- WILSON,., no date (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Souvenir book. Includes information about production and creative talents.
- WIZ, THE,., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- WIZARD OF OZ, THE,., 1939 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  Pamphlet programme. Includes text "Facts from the world of fancy." Front- collage of pictures of scenes, back-characiture illustration of main characters.
- WIZARD OF OZ, THE,., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Press material regarding the fiftieth anniversary of the Wizard of Oz.
- WIZARDS,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  One page programme and separate production information guide.
- WONDERFUL WORLD OF THE BROTHERS GRIMM, THE,., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Hard cover souvenir book. Includes captioned photos of scenes, production information and information about creative talents.
- WONDERS OF ALADDIN, THE,., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Fold-out center fold ad from Variety October 2, 1961.
- WORLD APART,., no date (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes and information about cast and creators.
- WORLD'S BEST,., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- YANKS,., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  One page programme. Includes picture of soldier and woman hugging.
- YOUNG WINSTON,., no date (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Souvenir book. Includes pictures of scenes, story summary, and information about major players.
- YOVITA,., no date (Box 2, Folder 37)
  Fold-out programme. Includes b/w pictures of scenes, story synopsis, and filmographies of director and key actors in French and English.